- Oh. Thank you, Penny.
- Mhmm.
(Sheldon:)Yeah, wait. Here.
(Sheldon:)For your troubles.
(Penny:)Oh, boy, a whole dollar.
(Penny:)Now I can quit my paper route.
(Penny:)So, what's in it?
(Leonard:)Doesn't matter. Half the time,
he just ends up playing with the box.
(Sheldon:)Yeah, it's journals and research papers
I wrote as a child.
(Penny:)Aw. How cute.
(Penny:)Is this, like, a diary?
No, that's my potty-training journal.
- Really? Your potty-training journal?
- Yeah.
(Sheldon:)And forgive my crude penmanship.
I didn't start typing until I was 6.
"August 7th, 8:42 a.m.
This is humiliating.
What was wrong with diapers?"
(Sheldon:)There are some charts in the back...
(Sheldon:)...where I kept track of shape,
color and consistency.
(Leonard:)Oh!
(Penny:)Disgusting.
(Leonard:)No, what's disgusting
is he's still keeping track.